ucraft.com 2019-05-29

# Privacy Policy | Ucraft

##### Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

 **Access to third-party accounts**

This type of service allows Ucraft to access Data from your account on a third-party service and perform actions with it.  
These services are not activated automatically, but require explicit authorization by the User.

 **Facebook account access (Ucraft)**

This service allows Ucraft to connect with the User's account on the Facebook social network, provided by Facebook, Inc.

Permissions asked: Email.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Analytics**

The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

 **Google Analytics (Google Inc.)**

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of Ucraft, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

 **Google Ads conversion tracking (Google Inc.)**

Google Ads conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Google Inc. that connects data from the Google Ads advertising network with actions performed on Ucraft.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

 **Commercial affiliation**

This type of service allows Ucraft to display advertisements for third-party products or services. Ads can be displayed either as advertising links or as banners using various kinds of graphics.  
Clicks on the icon or banner posted on the Application are tracked by the third-party services listed below, and are shared with Ucraft.  
For details of which data are collected, please refer to the privacy policy of each service.

 **iDevAffiliate (iDevDirect LLC)**

iDevAffiliate is a commercial affiliation service provided by iDevDirect LLC.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.idevdirect.com/policies.php).

 **Contacting the User**

 **Contact form (Ucraft)**

By filling in the contact form with their Data, the User authorizes Ucraft to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header.

Personal Data collected: company name, country, email address, first name, last name, phone number and website.

 **Mailing list or newsletter (Ucraft)**

By registering on the mailing list or for the newsletter, the User’s email address will be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning Ucraft. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to Ucraft or after making a purchase.

Personal Data collected: email address, first name and last name.

 **Content commenting**

Content commenting services allow Users to make and publish their comments on the contents of Ucraft.  
Depending on the settings chosen by the Owner, Users may also leave anonymous comments. If there is an email address among the Personal Data provided by the User, it may be used to send notifications of comments on the same content. Users are responsible for the content of their own comments.  
If a content commenting service provided by third parties is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the comment service is installed, even when Users do not use the content commenting service.

 **Disqus (Disqus)**

Disqus is a content commenting service provided by Big Heads Labs Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies, Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy) – [Opt out](https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/1657951).

 **Displaying content from external platforms**

This type of services allows you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of Ucraft and interact with them.  
This type of service might still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

 **Google Fonts (Google Inc.)**

Google Fonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows Ucraft to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.it/intl/policies/privacy/).

 **Handling payments**

Payment processing services enable Ucraft to process payments by credit card, bank transfer or other means. To ensure greater security, Ucraft shares only the information necessary to execute the transaction with the financial intermediaries handling the transaction.  
Some of these services may also enable the sending of timed messages to the User, such as emails containing invoices or notifications concerning the payment.

 **Braintree (PayPal Inc.)**

Braintree is a payment service provided by Braintree, a division of PayPal, Inc.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

 **Heat mapping and session recording**

Heat mapping services are used to display the areas of a page where Users most frequently move the mouse or click. This shows where the points of interest are. These services make it possible to monitor and analyze web traffic and keep track of User behavior.  
Some of these services may record sessions and make them available for later visual playback.

 **Hotjar Heat Maps & Recordings (Hotjar Ltd.)**

Hotjar is a session recording and heat mapping service provided by Hotjar Ltd.  
Hotjar honors generic „Do Not Track” headers. This means the browser can tell its script not to collect any of the User's data. This is a setting that is available in all major browsers. Find Hotjar’s [opt-out information here](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out).

Personal Data collected: Cookies, Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: Malta – [Privacy Policy](https://www.hotjar.com/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out).

 **Hosting and backend infrastructure**

This type of services has the purpose of hosting data and files that enable Ucraft to run and be distributed as well as to provide a ready-made infrastructure to run specific features or parts of Ucraft. Some of these services work through geographically distributed servers, making it difficult to determine the actual location where the Personal Data are stored.

 **Google App Engine (Google Inc.)**

Google App Engine is a hosting service provided by Google Inc.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/).

 **Google Cloud Storage (Google Inc.)**

Google Cloud Storage is a hosting service provided by Google Inc.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/).

 **Interaction with external social networks and platforms**

This type of services allow interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of Ucraft.  
The interaction and information obtained through Ucraft are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network.  
This type of service might still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

 **Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter, Inc.)**

The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/privacy).

 **Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets (Pinterest)**

The Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Pinterest platform provided by Pinterest Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy).

 **Registration and authentication**

By registering or authenticating, Users allow Ucraft to identify them and give them access to dedicated services.  
Depending on what is described below, third parties may provide registration and authentication services. In this case, Ucraft will be able to access some Data, stored by these third party services, for registration or identification purposes.

 **Google OAuth (Google Inc.)**

Google OAuth is a registration and authentication service provided by Google Inc. and is connected to the Google network.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://developers.google.com/accounts/docs/OAuth2).

 **Facebook Authentication (Facebook, Inc.)**

Facebook Authentication is a registration and authentication service provided by Facebook, Inc. and is connected to the Facebook social network.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/help/405977429438260).

 **Tag Management**

This type of service helps the Owner to manage the tags or scripts needed on Ucraft in a centralized fashion.  
This results in the Users' Data flowing through these services, potentially resulting in the retention of this Data.

 **Segment (Segment Inc.)**

Segment is a tag management service provided by Segment.io, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://segment.com/docs/legal/privacy/).

 **User database management**

This type of services allows the Owner to build user profiles by starting from an email address, a personal name, or other information that the User provides to Ucraft, as well as to track User activities through analytics features. This Personal Data may also be matched with publicly available information about the User (such as social networks' profiles) and used to build private profiles that the Owner can display and use for improving Ucraft.  
Some of these services may also enable the sending of timed messages to the User, such as emails based on specific actions performed on Ucraft.

 **Intercom (Intercom Inc.)**

Intercom is a User database management service provided by Intercom Inc. Intercom can also be used as a medium for communications, either through email, or through messages within our product(s).

Personal Data collected: email address and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://docs.intercom.io/pricing-and-terms/privacy).
